Previously on JoJo's Bizarre
Adventure... Ka. Choo! Aim. Beware!
Uh-oh. Him!
D. Oh.
Lloyd.
Servant!
Dio!
So then, where is Kakyoin?
He's with Jotaro.
Ooh!
Can I get some ice cream, please?
Welcome!
You know, ice cream is pretty good, but
this baby here, chilled coconut juice,?
nothing in the world like it.
How about it?
I guess we can try it.
Three, then. Thank you much!
That's $12!
Hey, Jerk!
What are you trying to pull?
Make it six!
Here.
This should cover it.
Okay, thanks! Enjoy!
I'll take that!
So, you dumb, useless,
disgusting piece of shit!
Who the hell do you think you are?
I'll make you wish you were never born!
Kakyoin!
Get up, you vile little cockroach dick!
Do I look like easy pickings to you?
And now, you'll feel the pain!
How dare you touch my wallet with the same
grimy fingers and wipe your filthy ass!
I can't let you get away with
something like that! Now can I?
Can I?
Kakyoin!
What are you doing to this guy?
You'll kill the bastard!
Come on, tell me, come on!
Kick
Now cut it out damn it.
You're losing control
We're acting like such a bastard.
Something's not right.
What the hell's gotten into you?
That hurt, you know.
You didn't have to shove me around
like you're the one in charge.
That man tried to steal my wallet.
He was committing a crime.
And criminals should be punished.
Tell me, am I wrong, Jotaro?
You'd do the same, old pal.
This guy...
Let's go.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
What are you glaring at?
You know, the look in your eyes
is awfully hostile, Jotaro.
What's wrong?
Why are you so upset?
You couldn't possibly be
thinking about ending our
friendship over a little
tussle with a thief now,
would you?
You're acting as if I've
done something unforgivable.
Defeat!
That's awesome!
Oh, wow! I see them!
There's four of them up there!
So cool!
Jojo!
You're making way too big
of a deal out of this.
I'm just having a bad day. No big thing.
I'm so exhausted from the trip.
It's put me in such a bad mood.
Just a bad mood, huh?
Seemed to me you felt pretty good.
The old man in Avdol think it's a good
idea for us to head to India by train.
We leave tomorrow.
We'll take the cable car to
Singapore Station to reserve tickets.
Come on, Kick!
Mr.
Kakaoing, Jojo's left already.
Shouldn't we get going?
Ah, right.
I'll catch up in just a second.
Oh, okay.
I guess you must like coconut
juice a whole lot, huh?
Was that a b-beetle?
No, no, I must be seeing things.
It must have been a piece
of coconut or something.
Oh, yes.
I do love coconuts.
They're my favorite.
What's up, Half-Pint?
Nothing, don't worry.
Hey, Jotaro.
You gonna eat that cherry?
If not, then hand it over already.
I'm starving.
Uh-oh, better watch out, Jotaro.
No! Jotaro!
Good one, huh?
I'm only playing with you.
Good old Jotaro.
It's like he's a totally different person.
That look again!
What's with all this hardcore
glaring Jotaro, old pal?
Have you lost your sense of humor?
Get in, Kakyoin.
The cable car just got here.
Now I told you to get in.
See, I've got your ticket right here.
I'm gonna knock your crooked possessed
ass right into that cable car.
What the!
You're a bit off possessed isn't quite
the word want to give it another try?
Wait a minute.
This isn't Kakyoin.
Congrats on not being
as stupid as you look.
Though you still haven't realized my body's
been growing this whole time, have you?
All right, who are you?
Is he a stand? Can't be.
I was able to touch him just now.
Unless he's a stand I can
strike with my own fists?
Jojo!
I can merge with any
organic matter I consume.
I'm a stand anyone can see and touch.
Lucky them, don't you think?
I'm yellow temperance
of the temperance car.
Gaze upon my handsome face with envy!
Come now, Jotaro old pal.
Take a good look at your hand.
See that little bit of me?
It latched on when you hit me and
really doesn't want to let go.
I advise you not to touch, or
it'll go after your left hand too.
You should save your left
hand for picking your nose.
This stand is a slow eater, and the
more it eats, the bigger it gets.
You'll never get it off.
Crap, damn you!
Hurrah!
What do you mean, hurrah?
When I digest you, I'll shove your
own crap down your measly throat!
The hell?
This stuff burns!
Damn bastard!
Hey, is this Mr. Jojo's grandpa?
He needs your help.
Anne, tell me what's wrong.
It's Mr. Kakyoing.
What about Kakyoing?
It's true, seems he has betrayed us. Mr.
Kakyoing's face split
and now he's a giant.
But Mr.
Kakyoing wasn't Mr. Kakyoing.
He's a fake, Anne.
Jojo got attacked by some weird slime on
the cable car and now
it's eating his finger.
Calm down, Anne.
Where are you now?
I'm at the cable car
station at the train center.
He's being attacked!
Mr.
Kakyo-ing went crazy
and is attacking Jojo!
Hurry and come back to the
hotel as fast as you...
Did someone say my name just now?
Hmm?
Where the hell have you been?
Jojo left me behind, so I
was sunbathing by the pool.
With your school uniform on?
Yes, why not?
It's all right.
We have the real one here with us.
And be careful, this means
your Kakyo-ing is... A fake!
I told you that!
Oh, no!
JoJo just jumped out of the cable car!
Good freakin' grief.
This stand that fuses with
flesh, it's devouring my finger.
This could get bad.
First, I've gotta get this stuff off me.
Might be easier said than done.
It might mean I have to cut off my finger.
Ha, do you really think you got away?
Sorry to burst your bubble, old pal.
Now dig that earwax out of your
ears and listen up, hotshot.
Your time's run out, cause yellow
temperance has no weaknesses.
You didn't escape.
It's just that I don't have to chase you.
You're as good as dead.
This'll hurt like a son of a
bitch, but I don't have a choice.
Wait, what the hell?
The flame only made it grow bigger.
That was a bad idea.
Damn, I thought I had it!
Pardon me.
My goodness!
That's certainly a bizarre entrance.
Don't mind me.
Hey there, kid.
I'm gonna need to borrow your
popsicle for just a second.
Hold on, young man.
What is it you think you're
doing with that child?
Is this your kid?
No, he's not, but...
Then shut up, lady, and enjoy the scenery.
Sorry, kid.
When we get down to the bottom,
I'll buy you a new one, okay?
Whatever kind you want.
If I can't burn it off...
That bastard.
What?
Now it's forming needles and
digging even deeper into my hands.
You really are stupid.
Nothing will work on it,
not even fire and ice.
I told you before, didn't I?
You won't find a single weakness.
And now you're mine, you little shit.
Yurtha.
Papa, the puppy.
It's got our puppy.
You bastard.
You were already in this cable
car waiting for me, weren't you?
No, please. Don't hurt Poco!
Watch out! Don't pull him! Let go!
And now it's your turn to die!
Gyotaro, old pal!
You're fast, but...
I keep telling you I
don't have any weaknesses.
Are you even listening to me?
You dumbass redneck!
My stand is armor that
can also absorb power.
A defensive wall that can also attack.
No matter how fast you are,
no matter how strong or smart?
You think you are, against yellow
temperance, you are helpless.
There's no way you can defeat me.
You won't survive unless, of course,
you suck it up and take a
cleaver to your right hand.
Do you understand?
Try as hard as you want, but
you have no way of winning.
You're not getting out of this,
not until you're digested.
I'll eat you up!
Oh, good grief.
Huh?
You're right, you really
don't have any weaknesses.
Maybe you are the world's strongest.
And that's terrifying.
But I'll tell you, we Cujos...
No, wait.
I mean Joestars.
We use strategy to fight
our way past any obstacle.
You haven't won yet.
And I still have one
strategy left. Really?
And that's two.
And that's to...
Run away!
What the hell?
You're in the middle of being
eaten alive, you dumbass!
My stand's got a hole that you can't
escape, and you say you'll run away?
Don't make me laugh!
When I said run away...
I meant into the water!
Damn it! I...
I can't breathe!
You let your stand's guard
down to take a breath.
Your stand may be invincible,
but you sure as hell aren't.
If I destroy you, then
your stand dies too.
Do you understand?
Listen, I've had it up to here
with that Guccio mouth of yours.
Alright?
I just happen to be the type of guy
who takes these things to heart.
Oh, please stop it.
I can't fight anymore. I'm through.
My beautiful nose is completely shattered.
And my face is so messed up, they're
going to have to wire my jaw shut too.
It hurts. Spare me.
Dio, he paid me to do this.
Look, I don't plan on risking
my life going after you guys.
There, see?
I want something from you.
The other stand users, I
want all the info you've got.
But that's the one thing I can't
say, don't ask me that, please?
I won't do it, I mean I do have some
pride, you know, I just can't, okay?
Well okay then, that's honorable I
remember now, there are four of them, okay?
One is the emperor,
then hanged man and empress, and
the last one goes by death Got it,
and what about their powers?
Sorry, I don't know.
No, no, really, I honestly
don't know anymore.
Don't you see?
Stan users don't reveal their powers.
If they did, they'd be exposing
their weaknesses outright.
But I do know something.
Some witch taught Dio about stans, and her
son is one of the four coming after you.
His name is Centerfold.
He's unmistakable because
he has two right hands.
His card is the Hanged Man.
He's the one who killed Polnareff's
little sister, isn't he?
I've heard the occasional
rumor about his powers.
A mirror!
Apparently, he uses a mirror.
I haven't actually seen it.
But Polnareff has no chance of winning.
He's dead meat.
I just noticed something, Jotaro.
Looks like I've still
got some luck on my side.
Ha-ha-ha!
Sucks to be you!
See that drain over
there off to your right?
The one with all the blue crawdads?
Take a real good look.
Ha-ha-ha!
A manhole!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
That drain pipe connects to this manhole!
It's a perfect setup for
Yellow Temperance's power!
I'm gonna pull you in and hold you there!
No, you can't attack me, loser!
I guess what I told you about the man
with two right hands will go to waste!
You're not gonna be able to help
poor Polnareff, Jotaro Kujo!
Aren't I lucky to have this
drain to slurp you into?
And you thought you had me, didn't you?
Man, am I lucky!
Time to power off with some crustaceans!
This is gonna be fun!
I'll mess you up and turn you into jelly!
And when I kill you, Dio's gonna give
me a hundred million dollars! Ha ha!
A few minutes of brawling with
you and I will be set for life!
Aren't I lucky?
Tell me I'm lucky, you
ball-less little butt-munch!
Good grief, really.
When you're focused on everything else,
it's hard to observe yourself you don't
get it do you fine then i'll just beat
the lesson in your luck finally ran out
before you got away with only a broken nose
when i'm done you won't
have any bones left to break
what did he just do he
punched me with water
I was only kidding around, Mr. Jotaro.
I swear I was just
messing with you, buddy.
Didn't mean anything by it, okay?
Be cool, man, be cool.
It was just a prank.
Wait, hang on a second.
You're not thinking about
punching me anymore, are you?
I'm seriously injured here.
My nose is badly broken and my jaw
is going to have to be wired shut.
Just shut up already.
I have nothing more to say to you.
You're way too pathetic.
I'm done wasting my breath.
Good grief.
So we're finally heading to India.
And the man with the two right
hands is called Centerfold. Right.
By the way, where did Anne run off to?
She was hanging around Singapore Station
right before our train departed, but...
She vanished.
Remember, she came to
Singapore to meet her father.
I'm sure she found him.
Yeah, well, that story about her meeting
up with her dad sounded fishy to me.
I bet she's a runaway.
But it is a bit lonely without
that little rug rat, right, Jojo?
Hmm.
But that stand earlier was pretty creepy.
It freaks me out that a stand
could disguise himself as me.
You know, I've been thinking about it.
He must have transformed
when I left the hotel.
Jojo, those cherries,
are you gonna eat them?
Not to be greedy, but
they are my favorite.
Could I have one?
Yeah, sure.
You're the best.
Hey, look, Jojo.
Flamingos in flight.
Oh, good grief.
Ciao, ciao.
All the old paintings on the tomb,
they do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick?
They're falling down like a domino!
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got the money on
a bed Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling tight to the hook I say!
Walk
like
an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink then
they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books!
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings?
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say!
Walk like an Egyptian.
Somebody's already stolen my wallet.
I don't need any?
Tip! Tip!
If you don't give me tips,
you won't go to heaven, sir?
Hey kid, don't put your
nose all over my stuff!
Avdol!
So this is India? See?
Great country, isn't it?